export const questions = [
  {
    question: "_____ her name Eliza? No, _____ .",
    answers: ["is / from", " isn’t / from", "isn’t / in ", "aren’t / in"],
    answer: "Is / it isn't",
  },
  {
    question: "I ... tennis every Sunday morning.",
    answers: ["playing", "play", " am playing", " am play"],
    answer: "play",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Don't make so much noise. Noriko ...... to study for her ESL test!",
    answers: ["try", "tries", "tried", "	is trying"],
    answer: "	is trying",
  },
  {
    question: "Jun-Sik .... his teeth before breakfast every morning.",
    answers: [" will cleaned", "	is cleaning", "cleans", "clean"],
    answer: "cleans",
  },
  {
    question: "Sorry, she can't come to the phone. She ..... a bath!",
    answers: ["is having", "having", "have", "has"],
    answer: "is having",
  },
  {
    question: "..... many times every winter in Frankfurt.",
    answers: [" It snows", "	It snowed", "	It is snowing", "	It is snow"],
    answer: "It snows",
  },
  {
    question: "How many students in your class ..... from Korea?",
    answers: ["comes", "come", "came", "are coming"],
    answer: "come",
  },
  {
    question: ` Weather report: "It's seven o'clock in Frankfurt and ..... ."`,
    answers: [" there is snow", " it`s snowing", "it snows", "it snowed"],
    answer: "it`s snowing",
  },
  {
    question: "Babies ..... when they are hungry.",
    answers: ["cry", "cries", "cried", "  are crying"],
    answer: "cry",
  },
  {
    question: ` What ..... in the evenings?"
    Mary: "Usually I watch TV or read a book.`,
    answers: ["you doing", "you do", "do you do", "	are you doing"],
    answer: "do you do",
  },
  {
    question: ` What ..... ?"
    Mary: "I'm trying to fix my calculator..`,
    answers: ["you doing", "you do", "do you do", "are you doing"],
    answer: "are you doing",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Jane ..... her blue jeans today, but usually she wears a skirt or a dress.",
    answers: ["wears", "wearing", "wear", " is wearing"],
    answer: "is wearing",
  },
  {
    question:
      "	I think I ..... a new calculator. This one does not work properly any more.",
    answers: ["needs", "needed", "need", "am needing"],
    answer: "need",
  },
  {
    question: "Sorry, you can't borrow my pencil. I ..... it myself.	",
    answers: ["was using", "using", " use", " am using"],
    answer: "am using",
  },
  {
    question: `At a school dance:
    Jane: " ..... yourself?"
    Mary: "Yes, I'm having a great time!"`,
    answers: ["You enjoying", "Enjoy you", "Do you enjoy", " Are you enjoying"],
    answer: "Are you enjoying",
  },
  {
    question: "What time .....",
    answers: [
      "the train leaves?",
      "leaves the train?",
      "  is the train leaving?",
      "does the train leave?",
    ],
    answer: "does the train leave?",
  },
  {
    question: "What time .....",
    answers: [
      "the train leaves?",
      "leaves the train?",
      "  is the train leaving?",
      "does the train leave?",
    ],
    answer: "does the train leave?",
  },
  {
    question: "You can keep my iPod if you like. I ..... it any more.",
    answers: [" don`t use", " doesn`t use", "   didn`t use", "  am not using"],
    answer: "don`t use",
  },
  {
    question: "I ..... for my pen. Have you seen it?",
    answers: ["will look", "    looking", "look", "am looking"],
    answer: "am looking",
  },
  {
    question: "The phone ...... Can you answer it, please?",
    answers: ["rings", "ring", "rang", " is ringing"],
    answer: "is ringing",
  },
];
